

ANYA POPOVA

DATA SCIENTIST • BARCELONA • (+34) 652 687 498

• DETAILS •

Barcelona (+34) 652 687 498 anya.chocolat@gmail.com

SKILLS

Python

Data Analysis

Pandas, NumPy

MySQL, MongoDB, Neo4j

Statistical Modeling and Analysis

Machine Learning

Scikit, TensorFlow, Keras, PyTorch

Data Visualization

Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly

Data Cleaning and Preprocessing

Pentaho DI, Power BI

Relational/Non-Relational DBs

Java

Complex Problem Solving

Strong Analytical Thinking Skills

Project Management

Communication Skills

LANGUAGES

English

Spanish

Russian

Catalan

• LINKS •

<u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

PROFILE

I am a beginner data scientist with over 10 years of experience in architecture and interior design. My passion for digital transformation and smart city technologies led me to pursue a career in data science, and I recently completed a data science bootcamp to gain the skills needed to enter this exciting field and I keep learning and expanding my skill set. As a collaborative problem-solver with a proven track record of delivering successful projects on time and within budget, I am confident that my unique blend of skills and experience will enable me to make a valuable contribution to any team.

★ PERSONAL PROJECTS

Genshin Impact Party Wiki

March 2023

A web page that will help Genshin Impact players create the perfect party for their battles, allowing me to apply my data science skills to a fun and engaging real-world problem.

GitHub repo

Exploring Job Market Trends in Russia through HeadHunter.ru Data Analysis

December 2022

The project includes data cleaning and preparation, exploratory data analysis and visualization. The goal of the project is to gain insights into the job market trends.

GitHub repo

CRM for a Trucking Company

October 2022

My team and I developed a trucking company CRM using Java and Spring Boot with back-end functionalities, such as customer management, order tracking, and reporting.

GitHub repo

EDUCATION

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} \textbf{Data Science Program, Bertelsmann Next Generation Tech Booster Scholarship , online } \\ \textbf{September 2022-Present} \end{tabular}$

Data Science Bootcamp, Ironhack, online

January 2023 — March 2023

Back End Web Development with Java Bootcamp, Ironhack, Barcelona

September 2022 — October 2022

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Technical Architect at Lázaro Rosa-Violán

September 2021 — August 2022

Team Leader at Intercon

October 2017 — August 2021